Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Paper Production Materials, 1979¯2001
  - El Diablo Nunca Duerme, 1994
    - International Festivals: 42nd Sydney Film Festival ¯ Sydney, Australia, 8/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 56)
    - International Festivals: 44th Melbourne International Film Festival ¯ Melbourne, Australia, 6/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 57)
    - International Festivals: 27th Aukland Film Festival ¯ New Zealand (Carton 4, Folder 58)
    - International Festivals: XVII Festival International de Cine Latinoamericano, Cuba, 12/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 59)
    - International Festivals: X Muestra de Cine Mexicano ¯ Guadalajara, Mexico, nd (Carton 4, Folder 61)
    - International Festivals: el Amante Cine Magazine Festival de Fortaleza, Brazil, 7/1997 (Carton 4, Folder 62)
    - International Festivals: Sao Paulo Film Festival ¯ Mostra International ¯ Brazil, 1995¯1996 (Carton 4, Folder 63)
    - International Festivals: Hamburg, Germany, 1996 (Carton 4, Folder 64)
    - International Festivals: Festival International de Biarritz ¯ France, 1996 (Carton 4, Folder 65)
    - International Festivals: Association Rencontres Cinemas d'Amerique Latine de Toulouse ¯ france, 1994 (Carton 4, Folder 66)
    - International Festivals: Association Rencontres Cinemas d'Amerique Latine de Toulouse, 1/1996 (Carton 4, Folder 67)
    - International Festivals: Tage des Unabhangigen Films ¯ Augsburg, Germany, 1996 (Carton 4, Folder 68)
    - International Festivals: Thessaloniki International Film Festival, Greece, 11/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 69)
    - International Festivals: 11th London lesbian & Gay Film Festival, London, 3/1997 (Carton 4, Folder 70)
    - International Festivals: 7th Latin American Film Festival ¯ London, 9/1996 (Carton 4, Folder 71)
    - International Festivals: San Juan Cinemafest ¯ Puerto Rico, 1995 (Carton 4, Folder 72)
    - International Festivals: III Mostra Internacional ¯ Barcelona, Spain, 1995 (Carton 4, Folder 73)
    - International Festivals: Huelva, Spain, 11/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 74)
    - International Festivals: 24th Wellington Film Festival participation ¯ certificate, 7/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 75)
    - International Festivals: Toronto International Film Festival, 9/1994 (Carton 4, Folder 76)
    - International Festivals: Toronto international Film Festival participation certificate, 9/1994 (Carton 4, Folder 77)
    - USA Film Festivals: The Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, San Antonio, Texas ¯ 18th edition, 2/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 78)
    - USA Film Festivals: 11th Chicago Latino Film Festival, 3/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 79)
    - USA Film Festivals: Mesilla Valley Film Society, New Mexico 1st Annual Border Festival, 9/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 80)
    - USA Film Festivals: Lycoming College: Women's Film Festival ¯ Williamsport, PA, 11/1996¯1/1997 (Carton 4, Folder 81)
    - USA Film Festivals: Mexican Fine Arts Center Museum, Chicago, IL., 11/1996 (Carton 4, Folder 82)
    - USA Film Festivals: 1997 ¯ 5th New England Latin American Film Festival (Carton 4, Folder 83)
    - USA Film Festivals: Arts of the Americas Annual Summer Festival, NY, NY, 5/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 84)
    - USA Film Festivals: Newport Beach International Film Festival, CA, 3/1996 (Carton 4, Folder 85)
    - USA Film Festivals: Festival de Cine ¯ UC Santa Cruz, CA, 5/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 86)
    - USA Film Festivals: 1st Annual las Memorias Occidental College ¯ LA, CA, 5/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 87)
    - USA Film Festivals: International House, Philadelphia, PA, 1994 (Carton 4, Folder 88)
    - USA Film Festivals: Cinequest ¯ San Jose, CA, 2/1996 (Carton 4, Folder 89)
    - USA Film Festivals: Rejects for festivals, etc., nd (Carton 4, Folder 90)
    - Screenings: Very 1st screening: PFA, 4/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 91)
    - Screenings: Other screenings, 1995¯1996 (Carton 4, Folder 92)
    - Screenings: College of Santa Fe, Santa Fe, N.M., 4/1998 (Carton 4, Folder 93)
    - Screenings: Conteht Studio Screening, 11/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 94)
    - Screenings: Fine Arts Cinema, Berkeley, CA, 2/1999 (Carton 4, Folder 95)
    - Screenings: Fine Arts Cinema, Berkeley, CA, 10/1999 (Carton 4, Folder 96)
    - Screenings: Independent Feature Film Market, 9/1994 (Carton 4, Folder 97)
    - Screenings: Independent Feature Project (screening) NY, NY, 8/1994 (Carton 4, Folder 98)
    - Screenings: Miscellaneous events, nd (Carton 4, Folder 99)
    - Screenings: New Films from Latin American ¯ University of Michigan, 3/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 100)
    - Screenings: Pacific Film Archive ¯ UC Berkeley, 4/1995 (Carton 4, Folder 101)
    - Screenings: Roxie Cinema, San Francisco, CA, nd (Carton 4, Folder 102)
    - Screenings: UCLA Film Conference, Los Angeles, CA, 5/1998 (Carton 4, Folder 103)
    - Screenings: University of Kansas, 3/1999 (Carton 4, Folder 104)
    - Screenings: Workshop with Ms. Portillo, 7/1996 (Carton 4, Folder 105)
    - Screenings: XXV Congreso National Associaton for Chicana & Chicano Studies (NACCS), 6/1998 (Carton 4, Folder 106)
    - Screenings: UC Davis ¯ NACCS Studies Conference held in Mexico, 1/1998 (Carton 4, Folder 107)
    - Screenings: Hispanic Heritage Month ¯ Smithonian Institution, Washington, D.C., 7/1998 (Carton 4, Folder 108)
    - Screenings: Screen International, NY, NY, 9/1994 (Carton 4, Folder 109)
    - Professional Correspondence: Fundacion Antorchas, 11/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 1)
    - Professional Correspondence: Professional Correspondence, 1995 & 3/1998 (Carton 5, Folder 2)
    - Professional Correspondence: Elena Feder, PH.D, Simon Fraser University, Burnaby, B.C., 5/1998 (Carton 5, Folder 3)
    - Professional Correspondence: Tere Toledo (Carton 5, Folder 4)
    - Professional Correspondence: Vendor I.D. Profile: Duke University (Carton 5, Folder 5)
    - Other: Critical Study: "Photography, Identity, and Death in the Films of Lourdes Portillo" by Barbara McBane (Carton 5, Folder 6)
    - Other: The Photographic Image in the Films of Lourdes Portillo ¯ by Barbara McBane, nd (Carton 5, Folder 7)
    - Other: "An Evening with Filmmaker Lourdes Portillo", nd (Carton 5, Folder 8)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as panelist at the 22nd Annual Cinefestival, San Antonio, TX, 6/1999 (Carton 5, Folder 9)
    - Other: Context discussion with: Electra Arenal ¯ Latinamericanist ¯ Cornell University, New York, 1/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 10)
    - Other: Guest speaker: University of New Mexico in Albuquerque, 4/1998 (Carton 5, Folder 11)
    - Other: KPFA interview with Ms. Portillo, San Francisco, CA, 5/1998 (Carton 5, Folder 12)
    - Other: The Library Media Project, Washington, D.C.: dinner for members of governing and advisory board, 6/1998 (Carton 5, Folder 13)
    - Other: "Parallels & Intersections" ¯ book & exhibition: Creative Arts Enterprises, San Francisco, CA, 11/1999 (Carton 5, Folder 14)
    - Other: "Sacando Los Trapos Al Aire" commentary by Rosa Linda Fregoso, 3/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 15)
    - Other: Critical retrospective study on Ms. Portillo's work by Rosa Linda Fregoso (Carton 5, Folder 16)
    - Other: "Diablos y fantasmas" Rosa Linda (Carton 5, Folder 17)
    - Other: University of Buenos Aires ¯ Jorge la Ferla: Spanish commentary, nd (Carton 5, Folder 18)
    - Other: Miscellaneous cinema history momentos, i.e., Luis Valdez' 50th birthday invitation, etc., nd (Carton 5, Folder 19)
    - Other: Dr. Loco: Musica Chicano ¯ Yerba Buena Center, San Francisco, ca, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 20)
    - Other: Other engagements, 1996 (Carton 5, Folder 21)
    - Other: Cine Siglo conference, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 22)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as guest speaker, 9/1994 (Carton 5, Folder 23)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as juror at Sundance, 1996 (Carton 5, Folder 24)
    - Other: Faxes, nd (Carton 5, Folder 25)
    - Other: Pictures from "The Devil..." poster, nd (Carton 5, Folder 26)
    - Other: "Diablo" Reviews, nd (Carton 5, Folder 27)
    - Other: "Devil" Que Sheets, nd (Carton 5, Folder 28)
    - Awards/Sweet Letters: Most Promising Latino Filmmaker ¯ Fox Latin American Channel, 9/1994 (Carton 5, Folder 29)
    - Awards/Sweet Letters: Awards: International Documentary Association ¯ Los Angeles, CA, 10/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 30)
    - Awards/Sweet Letters: Goldies '97: The Guardian Outstanding Local Discovery Awards, 1997 (Carton 5, Folder 31)
    - Awards/Sweet Letters: 1995 Taos Talking Picture Festival Award (Carton 5, Folder 32)
    - Awards/Sweet Letters: Appreciation letters, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 33)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Retrospective of Ms. Portillo's work at the University at Buffalo, New York, 11/1999 (Carton 5, Folder 34)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Retrospective on Ms. Portillo's work, spain, 1999 (Carton 5, Folder 35)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Context Studios ¯ NY, NY, 1996 (Carton 5, Folder 36)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Assorted screenings, 1994¯1995 (Carton 5, Folder 37)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1996 (Carton 5, Folder 38)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Screening comments, 1994 (Carton 5, Folder 39)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: POV submission form, NY, NY, 10/1994 (Carton 5, Folder 40)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Screening attendance report (Carton 5, Folder 41)
    - Exhibitions/Screenings: Chicano Now ¯ San Antonio, 2/2002 (Carton 5, Folder 42)
    - Distribution: 1996 distribution folder (Carton 5, Folder 43)
    - Distribution: Individual request for video, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 44)
    - Distribution: Henry Art Gallery poster, nd (Carton 5, Folder 45)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: New Directors/New Films, 3/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 46)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Hot Springs Documentary Film Festival ¯ 1996 (Carton 5, Folder 47)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 8emes Rencontres Cinemas d'Amerique Latine ¯ Toulouse, France, 8/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 48)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Lateinamerika ¯ Filmtage, Mexico ¯ Hamburg, Germany, 1996 (Carton 5, Folder 49)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 27th Auckland International Film Festival, 7/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 50)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 3a Mostra International de Films de Dones ¯ Barcelona Spain, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 51)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: SCS annual conference, University of North Texas, Texas, 3/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 52)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Universidad de Buenos Aires, 12/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 53)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Mostra Latino¯Americana do Rio de Janeiro, 6/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 54)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 6th annual Xicano/Latino Film Festival ¯ UC Santa Cruz, California, 5/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 55)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 36th London Film Festival, 11/1992 (Carton 5, Folder 56)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Muestra de Cine Mexicano en Guadalajara, 3/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 57)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 24th Wellington Film Festival, Wellington, New Zealand, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 58)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Le Nouveau Festival ¯ Montreal, 6/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 59)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Pacific Film Archive UC Berkeley, 4/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 60)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Artslink, Hong Kong, 9/1997 (Carton 5, Folder 61)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: San Francisco MOMA News, San Francisco, CA, 3/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 62)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: New Directors/New Films ¯ MOMA, San Francisco, ca, 3/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 63)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Center for the Arts ¯ Yerba Buena Center, San Francisco, ca, 4/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 64)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: The Brooklyn Museum ¯ a Festival of Latin American Cinema, 3/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 65)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 11th Chicago Latino Film Festival, 3/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 66)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 5th Annual Pacific Images Film Festival, Honolulu, Hawaii, 7/1998 (Carton 5, Folder 67)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Filmmaker ¯ The Magazine of Independent Film, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 68)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Veredas ¯ Revista do Centro Cultural Banco do Brasil, 6/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 69)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Cologne Conference, Cologne, Germany, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 70)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Sundance Film Festival ¯ Utah, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 71)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Sundance Film Festival ¯ Awards Night ¯ Utah, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 72)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Sundance Film Festival ¯ Utah, 1997 (Carton 5, Folder 73)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Sundance Film & Video Monthly ¯ Utah, 4/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 74)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Taos Talking Picture Festival, Taos, New Mexico, 4/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 75)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: The 7th Latin American Film Festival, London, England, 9/1996 (Carton 5, Folder 76)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Cinematheque, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Carton 5, Folder 77)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 19a Mostra Internacional de Cinema ¯ Sao Paulo ¯ Brazil, 11/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 78)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: San Juan Cinemafest, 10/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 79)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: International Documentary, Los Angeles, CA, 11/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 80)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 44th Melbourne International Film Festival, Melbourne, Australia, 6/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 81)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: Picture Talk ¯ San Francisco Film Society, 6/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 82)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: The Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center ¯ San Antonio, Texas, 2/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 83)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 11th Chicago Latino Film Festival, 3/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 84)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: 42nd Sydney Film Festival ¯ Sydney, Australia, 6/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 85)
    - Magazines re: Film Festivals and Screenings: San Francisco 38th International Film Festival, 5/1995 (Carton 5, Folder 86)
    - Production: Contents of Black Binder: Script (Carton 6, Folder 1)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 1¯5 (Carton 6, Folder 2)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 6¯10 (Carton 6, Folder 3)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 11¯15 (Carton 6, Folder 4)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 16¯20 (Carton 6, Folder 5)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 21¯25 (Carton 6, Folder 6)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 26¯30 (Carton 6, Folder 7)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 31¯35 (Carton 6, Folder 8)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 36¯41 (Carton 6, Folder 9)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 42¯49 (Carton 6, Folder 10)
    - Production: Contents of Grey Binder: Assembly Translation SR 44, 50B (Carton 6, Folder 11)
    - Production: Contents of White Binder: Promo Selects (Carton 6, Folder 12)
    - Production: Contents of Large Blue Binder: Unedited Transcripts (Carton 6, Folder 13)
    - Production: Contents of Large Black Binder: "Working Scripts"¯Laura del Fuego, May 31, 1994 (Carton 6, Folder 14)
    - Production: Contents of Large Black Binder: "Working Scripts"¯Act I (Carton 6, Folder 15)
    - Production: Contents of Large Black Binder: "Working Scripts"¯Act II (Carton 6, Folder 16)
    - Production: Contents of Large Black Binder: "Working Scripts"¯Act III (Carton 6, Folder 17)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR 1¯10 (Carton 6, Folder 18)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR 11¯20 (Carton 6, Folder 19)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR 21¯30 (Carton 6, Folder 20)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR 31¯40 (Carton 6, Folder 21)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR 41¯50 (Carton 6, Folder 22)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR 50B (Carton 6, Folder 23)
    - Production: Contents of Large White Binder: "Transcripts" SR B1¯B5 (Carton 6, Folder 24)
    - Production: Contents of Brown Binder: "Unedited Transcripts" (Carton 6, Folder 25)
    - Production: Contents of Green Binder: "Script for Michelle Valladares" ¯ Letter from Linda Seger¯Script Consultant, 5/1994 (Carton 6, Folder 26)
    - Production: Contents of Green Binder: "Script for Michelle Valladares" ¯ Act I, 5/1994 (Carton 6, Folder 27)
    - Production: Contents of Green Binder: "Script for Michelle Valladares" ¯ Act II, 5/1994 (Carton 6, Folder 28)
    - Production: Contents of Green Binder: "Script for Michelle Valladares" ¯ Act III, 5/1994 (Carton 6, Folder 29)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR 1¯10 (Carton 6, Folder 30)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR 11¯20 (Carton 6, Folder 31)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR 21¯30 (Carton 6, Folder 32)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR 31¯40 (Carton 6, Folder 33)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR 41¯50 (Carton 6, Folder 34)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR 50B (Carton 6, Folder 35)
    - Production: Contents of Red Binder; Sound Reel's Transcriptions SR B1¯B5, 7A (Carton 6, Folder 36)
    - Production: Yellow Re¯recording logs: Reels 1¯4, nd (Carton 7, Folder 1)
    - Production: Yellow Re¯recording logs: Reel 2 ADR, nd (Carton 7, Folder 2)
    - Production: Yellow Re¯recording logs: Reel 4, nd (Carton 7, Folder 3)
    - Production: Yellow Re¯recording logs: Reel 4, nd (Carton 7, Folder 4)
    - Production: Sound Scripts (Carton 7, Folder 5)
    - Production: 1996 Office Calendar: January to June, 1996 (Carton 7, Folder 6)
    - Stills of Film Frames used in editing, nd; 673.0 Items (Carton 39, Sleeve 1¯323)
  - Sor Juana: The Tenth Muse
    - Proposals: NEH Grant Proposal ¯ #1, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 1)
    - Proposals: 1991¯1992 NEH Grant Paperwork/Proposal ¯ #2, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 2)
    - Proposals: NEH Proposal, Copies, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 3)
    - Proposals: Writer's Contract, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 4)
    - Proposals: Team's Curriculum Vitae & Letters of Commitment, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 5)
    - Proposals: NEH Phone Directory & FAF Grant Due Dates, 7/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 6)
    - Proposals: Advisory Board, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 7)
    - Budget: Sor Juana ¯ Budget, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 8)
    - Budget: 1994 NEH Budget, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 9)
    - Budget: NEH: 1993 Final Budget, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 10)
    - Budget: NEH: Sor Juana, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 11)
    - Budget: Deposits ¯ Budget, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 12)
    - Budget: FAF Sponsorship, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 13)
    - Budget: Petty Cash, 2/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Olivia Crawford ¯ Writer's Invoice, 3/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 15)
    - Budget: Travel to Scholar's Meeting, 5/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 16)
    - Research: Ms. Portillo's Calendar, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 17)
    - Research: Scholar's Research, 3/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 18)
    - Research: History of Project, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 19)
    - Research: Professional Correspondence/Scholars: Letters of Commitment, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 20)
    - Research: Advisors' Letters of Commitment ¯ Originals, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 21)
    - Research: Articles & Papers, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 22)
    - Research: Lucciani's Articles on SJ: Originals, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 23)
    - Research: Meeting W/scholars Re: Sor Juana, 2/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 24)
    - Research: Misc. Scholars' Correspondence, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 25)
    - Research: Copies of Scholar's Curriculum Vitae, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 26)
    - Research: Electra Arenal, Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 27)
    - Research: Electra Aranal, Advisor: Articles/Spanish, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 28)
    - Research: Jean Franco, Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 29)
    - Research: Fred Luciani, Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 30)
    - Research: Stephanie Merrim, Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 31)
    - Research: Georgina Sabat Rivers, Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 32)
    - Research: Elias Trabulse, Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 33)
    - Research: Laurie Coyle: Various Letters To, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 34)
    - Scripts: NEH: Olivia Crawford ¯ Treatment, 1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 35)
    - Scripts: Correspondence From & To Olivia Crawford, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 36)
    - Scripts: Readings ¯ Spanish: Georgia Sabat¯Rivers, Frederick, Luciani, Ivan A. Schulman¯Evelyn Picon Garfield, Margo Glantz, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 37)
    - Scripts: Sabat Rivers' Article ¯ Spanish, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 38)
    - Scripts: Frederick Luciani's Article ¯ English, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 39)
    - Scripts: Music ¯ Sor Juana, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 40)
    - Professional Correspondence: Karen Fuglie, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 41)
    - Professional Correspondence: Concepcion R. Bernal, 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 42)
    - Professional Correspondence: New York Meeting, 2/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 43)
    - Exhibitions: Schedule, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 44)
    - Exhibitions: Festival ¯ Chicago, Ill, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 45)
    - Exhibitions: Homenaje International ¯ Mexico, 11/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 46)
    - Exhibitions: City University of New York, NYC, NY, 10/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 78, Folder 47)
  - Sometimes My Feet Go Numb
    - Introduction on Ms. Portillo, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 59)
    - Proposal: Grants, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 60)
    - Proposal: AIDS Film Contract, 7/1989; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 61)
    - Production: Credits, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 62)
    - Publicity: ITVS News Release: "Positive Life with HIV", 1995; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 63)
    - Publicity: ITVS Coming Attractions ¯ Programmer's Update, 6/1995; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 64)
    - Publicity: Organizing Kit, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 65)
    - Glossies: Positive: Life with HIV, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 66)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 67)
    - Exhibitions: List of Festival Screenings, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 68)
    - Exhibitions: Sometimes... Festivals, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 69)
    - Exhibitions: A Gliff: Austin Gay & Lesbian International Film Festival, 7/1996; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 70)
    - Exhibitions: Mix '96: 10th New York Lesbian & Gay Film/Video Festival, 8/1996; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 71)